[{"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438192", "answer": "Antwort 0", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 0", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438237", "answer": "Antwort 1", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 1", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438248", "answer": "Antwort 2", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 2", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438256", "answer": "Antwort 3", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 3", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438264", "answer": "Antwort 4", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438272", "answer": "Antwort 5", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 5", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438280", "answer": "Antwort 6", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 6", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438287", "answer": "Antwort 7", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 7", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438295", "answer": "Antwort 8", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 8", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438303", "answer": "Antwort 9", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 9", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438311", "answer": "Antwort 10", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 10", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438319", "answer": "Antwort 11", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 11", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438327", "answer": "Antwort 12", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 12", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438335", "answer": "Antwort 13", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 13", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438346", "answer": "Antwort 14", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 14", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438355", "answer": "Antwort 15", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 15", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438363", "answer": "Antwort 16", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 16", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438371", "answer": "Antwort 17", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 17", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438379", "answer": "Antwort 18", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 18", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438387", "answer": "Antwort 19", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 19", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438395", "answer": "Antwort 20", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 20", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438402", "answer": "Antwort 21", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 21", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438410", "answer": "Antwort 22", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 22", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438418", "answer": "Antwort 23", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 23", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438428", "answer": "Antwort 24", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 24", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438436", "answer": "Antwort 25", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 25", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438444", "answer": "Antwort 26", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 26", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438452", "answer": "Antwort 27", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 27", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438460", "answer": "Antwort 28", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 28", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 23:13:28.438467", "answer": "Antwort 29", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "Frage 29", "learned": false}]